So first let's understand what a
Hermes agent is.
Hermes agent is one of the top open
source projects from Nous Research.
So this is a persistent agent,
not a chatbot.
We have ChatGPT, Claude,
etc.
You will go to the web page and you
will chat.
If you give a task, it will do the
task.
But this is completely opposite to
those things.
This is a continuous agent that will
run on your server 24x7.
Along with that, it can write its
own skill as well.
And one of the best thing is,
this agent can work with any kind of
LLM.
Anthropic, OpenAI, Google,
OpenRouter, Ollama, LLMs that you
have self -hosted.
It can run on any kind of LLM.
You don't need to pay and use free API
keys if you want.
And that is why it has become so
popular these days.
And one more best thing is,
you can communicate via this agent
using 20 plus different messaging
platforms.
Telegram, WhatsApp, Slack,
you can use any kind of messaging
platform.
And one more best thing is,
it is not only just for developers.
Because with zero coding skills,
you can build your own agent.
You can build your own personal
assistant.
Let me repeat once again.
With zero coding language
experience, you can build your own
agent.
Isn't it amazing? Isn't it
interesting?
And one more thing is, you can
directly communicate with this agent
using plain English.
You don't have to know how much
coding you have to do.
You don't have to understand what is
happening inside.
You don't need to do any of those
things.
You can directly speak to it just
like normal English.
And it will handle all the tech for
you.
In the back -end, you don't have to
do any code execution or task
execution.
You don't have to do any of those
things.
You just need to say, I have to do
this and it will do that.
And it will work for you 24x7.
Whether you are sleeping,
playing or playing, this agent will
continue to run on its server 24x7.
Those are all the best things that
this agent can do.
And after that, there are five core
components to this agent.
First thing is memory.
So let's say, you hired a personal
assistant.
After 2 -3 months, that personal
assistant will get to know what you
like, what you don't like, what you
do, how your meetings are,
what to do and what not to do.
He will remember every single thing,
right?
Similarly, our Hermes agent also has
something called as memory.
What it does in this is, it will
remember all of your details.
Your name, what you do,
where you are, what things you like,
what things you don't like,
what you do daily, every single
thing.
It is just like your personal
assistant.
And after that, we have something
called as skills.
And by default, when you install
Hermes agent, they come with 100
plus skills installed,
guys.
It has a skill to create PDFs.
It has a skill to send emails.
It has a skill to check calendars.
I mean, you can do a lot of stuff
and you can write your own skills as
well.
That is the best part.
And the next important thing,
which is called as soul.
So before that, I want to tell you a
small story.
So before Hermes agent,
we have one more agent which is
called OpenClaw.
So what is the difference between
OpenClaw and this?
There are two things.
One is soul and the other is
self-improving.
I will talk about self-improving in some
time.
What is soul?
Let me tell you an example.
You hire a personal assistant.
Sometimes a personal assistant can
be rude by default.
Maybe he can be loving.
Maybe he is professional.
So they have their persona,
right?
Similarly, you can put your persona
for this Hermes agent.
Maybe you want your agent to talk
lovely to you.
professionally.
Maybe you want your agent to be
rude, critique.
There are so many personas that you
can build for your agent.
And if you use this agent,
this persona will also get enhanced
as well by default.
And how does that happen?
That is what we will talk about in
self-improving.
And then next we have the important
stuff, which are called cron jobs.
What are cron jobs?
Let's say you have to read the
newspaper every morning.
So you read the newspaper every
morning at 7 o 'clock.
Similarly, you want this agent to
execute the same job at every day or
at any specific time.
So for example, when I wake up in
the morning, I want the agent to
scrape through all the news on the
internet regarding AI.
And it should give me the top 5
topics that I need to read about.
So what happens because of this?
I can keep up with the trends that
are going with the AI.
And I don't have to do any research
for this.
When I sleep, it will do all the
research.
By the time I wake up,
it will give me the summary.
Isn't it interesting?
And the next thing is self-improving.
What is self-improving?
Let's say you are using this agent
and you are doing the same things
again and again.
So what does this do?
It will observe that pattern and it
will create a skill for that
automatically for you.
And you use it and all of these
files will get enhanced.
Whether it's memory, skills,
skills, cron jobs, it will suggest
every single thing.
So that is why it is so powerful.
And it is one of the most open
source projects right now in the
agentic space.
And the next thing is what is inside
this agent, Mr. Balaji?
That is a valid question.
So let me show you exactly how it
looks like.
Not exactly how it looks like.
I will show you how our UI looks
like.
But think about it like this.
Let's say our Hermes agent is also a
source.
Inside this, we have soul.md.
So if you know about agents,
you save all the information in the
md files or markdown files.
So what does soul.md do?
It will save your personality and
tone.
And config.aml.
It will remember your MCPs,
tools, skills and all of that stuff.
And.environment file.
What does this environment file do?
It will save all of your passwords,
tokens, authentication,
JSONs, a lot of stuff.
And then we have memory.
It will have user memory and normal
project memory.
And then we have skills.
I told you, right?
I need to be brief every morning.
So I have morning brief and email
triage.
If I want to send some emails to a
lot of people, I can use this.
And then what are our cron jobs?
Every day, what work should I
execute at what time?
And then we have sessions as well.
So all of these things will lie
inside your Hermes agent.
And inside this, there are two
different files inside memory.
One is user.md and another is memory
.md.
What does this user.md do?
It will save all the details about
me.
For example, I am Balaji Chepada.
Lead data sender.
My timezone is CEST.
What do I do?
I want everything to be concise.
I don't want any of the random
things.
And everything...
What I am saying is that I want
everything to be in bullet points.
And then normal memory.md.
What does this do?
My projects, my environment,
everything.
It will keep updating all of these
things.
So it is like you are training your
own assistant.
You are trying to use this.
That is why it is so powerful.
And then this is the best thing.
It gets better as you use it.
You will do a job.
And the agent will learn that job.
And it will save it to the memory.
And it will build skills to automate
that task.
And it will search for the past
work.
And it will repeat all of that
stuff.
It will automate the big job you are
repeating by default for you.
You don't need to do extra work.
And why a VPS is required?
What is a VPS?
So what is a VPS?
It is a virtual private server.
So let's say you have installed this
Hermes agent in your laptop.
So your laptop should always be
connected to power.
It should be connected to internet.
It should also keep running your
agent.
So this is 24x7.
Your agent will work only if the
laptop is on.
So it is very difficult,
right?
That is why you can use a virtual
private server called VPS.
What does it do?
It will run your agent 24x7.
No matter how your laptop is.
It will work in the cloud.
So you don't need to worry about it.
And then unreliable uptime.
When you are at home, you may run
out of power, Wi -Fi, or OS updates.
All of these things will happen.
But if you are in a VPS,
it has a very stable connection.
And since it is in the data center,
it will not have any of these
issues.
And after that, by executing this
agent in your laptop,
you are using hardware of your
laptop.
Battery, CPU, GPU, all of these
things will wear and tear along the
time.
So to avoid that, you can use VPS.
VPS costs are usually very low.
And then home network limits,
static IP and access.
And since this is your personal
machine,
giving an agent access to your
entire personal machine would be a
little bit scary.
So usually recommended in production
or office is always use sandboxes.
What is this sandbox?
That is what VPS is.
And you can use this VPS to install
your agent.
And if anything goes wrong tomorrow,
the data in that VPS will be
corrupted.
So your laptop is safe and secure.
That is why I recommend going via
VPS route.
Now for the actual setup.
Take a VPS server and install Hermes
agent.
For that, we are going to use a
website called Hostinger.
And before we proceed,
I want to mention this video is made
in partnership with Hostinger.
But honestly, even before this
collaboration,
I was already using Hostinger for my
own work and personal use case.
If you look at the email team at the
red balachipay.com
www.balachipay.com to get the
domain.
I have been using their products for
quite some time.
And I am happy to collaborate with
them.
And I will put the exact link to
this website in the description
below.
You can check it out.
And you get a 69 % off on AI managed
VPS hosting.
Virtual private server for more
power and control.
There are multiple plans KVM 1,
KVM 2, KVM 4 and KVM 8.
KVM 1 is very basic.
You cannot even use Hermes agent
properly in KVM 1.
So I would say at least go with KVM
2.
If you have a more powerful use
cases,
My recommendation is start with KVM
2.
And if you think it is doing good,
then upscale to KVM 4.
So KVM 2 will already get these kind
of benefits.
2 CPU cores, 8 GB RAM,
80 GB NVMe disk space and 8 TB
bandwidth.
So for the use case that I am going
to explain,
KVM 2 is good enough.
Let's go with KVM 2 plan.
And this is the payment summary
page.
Here you can choose the time period.
If you want to try it out for one
month,
You can choose one month.
But it is going to be costly 12.99
per month.
My recommendation is you can go with
24 months.
Because of this, your monthly bill
will become 799.
If you think this is a little more
time frame,
Then go with 12 months,
which will give you approximately
1000 rupees per month.
So my recommendation is go with 24
months.
And because we did a collaboration
with this video, Hostinger,
I do have a coupon code.
You can use my name as a coupon
code, which is called Balaji.
And I will put it in the description
below as well.
And you can apply and you will get
10 % off guys.
And you can continue and you can
make your payment from this page
itself.
After you have logged in.
And once you have made the payment,
You will land on this page.
You have to choose a server
location.
Usually choose the server or the
country which is very close to you.
Since I am in Europe, Germany is the
one which is close to me.
And if you are in India,
you can choose Mumbai or maybe
Malaysia.
But I would prefer choosing Mumbai.
So what I will do here, I will
choose Germany.
Because it is going to decide your
latency.
By saying that latency means how
fast the communication will be.
And I will click on next.
And here you can choose the OS.
Earlier we thought that VPS is
basically a server or a machine.
That is running on the cloud.
Then you need any kind of OS in that
machine.
And for popular OS like this,
click on Ubuntu and select.
And once you select that,
you will land on this page.
Here you need to create a password.
This is the root password.
That is going to be very important
for you.
Because once you create a VPS,
This is the password that it is
going to ask you to log in to the
VPS.
So I will put my password.
So let's say.
Okay.
Since I have given my password,
click on next.
I would say no thanks right now.
And here you can add additional
things like malware scanners or auto
backups.
Or I would prefer using Docker
manager.
What is Docker?
Inside this KVM server,
there is another container.
And choose the Docker manager.
And click on next.
Once you do this, it will start your
VPS server on the Hostinger panel.
And once you have completed that
process,
You will come to this page which is
called Hostinger hPanel.
If you want to find your VPS,
On the left side, you have something
which is called as VPS here.
And you can come to this page.
You can see here.
The plan you have taken is KVM2.
It is currently running.
You can click on manage.
And after that, on the left side,
you can see something which is
called as Docker manager.
You can see all the details here.
But let's not worry about all of
those things.
Click on Docker manager.
And here you can start with compose.
And you will say one click deploy.
So in Hostinger, one of the best
advantages is that
You can install your agents on the
Docker inside a KVM server.
With a single click.
What do we do here?
We will go with Hermes.
So in Hermes, we have multiple
things.
Hermes agent.
Hermes web UI.
And Hermes workspace.
So I would go ahead and go with
Hermes agent.
Because this is where you get more
power.
If you are a web person,
you can go with this one as well.
Or you can choose workspace.
But for this demo, I will go with
Hermes agent.
And just wanted to show you one more
thing.
There are so many different agents.
You can install Openclog.
There are lot of things that you can
do with one click deploy in
Hostinger.
So let's go with Hermes.
And I will click on select.
And look here.
This is what my admin username is.
I am putting my name Hermes here.
I will not worry about any of the
things.
This is my admin password.
Nexus API key.
You don't even need this actually.
So I will just remove this API key.
Because we are not going to use any
of the tokens from the Nexus.
So this is our admin password.
And I will click on deploy.
I will say save.
And wait.
What happens here is once it is
deployed.
You will get a terminal.
It is running and say.
Right now it is deployed.
That's why you are seeing open and
terminal.
You can click on open.
You don't need to even go to
terminal as well.
Give your username here.
What you can do if you forget your
password.
You can come back to the Hostinger
page.
You can click on manage.
And under this you have something
which is called as environment.
And I can click on my admin
password.
I will change the password later on.
So don't worry about this.
And I will paste my password here.
And click on sign in.
So no thanks.
And you can see here.
On the left side we have chart.
Sessions.
Models.
Logs.
Cron jobs.
Kills.
Plugins.
MCP.
Channels.
Webhooks.
Pairing.
Profiles.
Config.
Keys.
System.
Documentation.
So there are so many things that
this agent can do.
First what we will do is.
We will try to set it up.
And for setting it up.
You need to use a command.
Which is called as slash setup.
So click on enter.
So let me zoom in.
Look here.
What is asking here is.
If you want to go via quick setup or
full setup.
What we will do is.
We will go via full setup.
If you want to navigate here.
You can use up and down arrows.
If you space you can select.
And you can click on enter to choose
the option.
So I will now choose and enter.
And look here.
It is asking me to choose.
Which API I want to use with this.
So you can use OpenAI API.
Anthropic API.
OpenRouter API.
You can use as per your requirement.
So for now what I will do is.
I will go via Claude models.
From Anthropic.
So I will choose Anthropic.
Here we have three options.
Either if you have a Claude
subscription already.
You can use that.
If you don't have that.
You can use the API key as well.
And I will go via API key.
So what I did is.
Come to Claude website.
I created an API key.
Let me copy the API key.
And here.
I will choose the option 2.
Because I am going via API key.
And I will paste my API key.
Simple.
And after that.
It is asking.
In that Claude.
You are thinking to communicate with
812 model.
So 4.8 is too much powerful.
For my daily tasks.
So what I will do is.
I will go via 4.6.
Which is also from the Opus.
And what the terminal will do.
Keep the current local.
And after that.
The second best thing.
The Hermes agent can do is.
You can talk to Hermes agent.
With any of the messaging platforms
guys.
Once you have done all the setup.
You don't need to come back to setup
again.
Here.
We have options to telegram.
Slack.
Matrix.
WhatsApp.
Signal.
Email.
SMS.
There are so many options.
So what we will do.
We will go via telegram.
And to select it.
I am clicking space bar.
And click on enter.
What it is asking.
If you want to go via automatic or
manual.
So I will say.
I will go via automatic.
What I will do is.
I will open my camera.
I will scan this QR code.
And click on telegram.
And it will redirect me to the
telegram bot.
I will.
Open the telegram.
And here it is asking.
What is the bot name.
Let's say.
Hermes agent V1.
I will put it as version 1.
Let me create this.
And here our bot is created.
And I can start talking to this bot.
So I clicked start.
But it will not respond to us right
away.
Because we have such a setup.
So once it is done.
Look here.
Allow telegram.
To use this account.
I will say.
Yes.
Keep it here.
And.
If anyone else wants to add
additional user.
I don't know.
I don't want any additional user ID.
So I will.
Leave it as blank.
Enter it.
And user ID is asking.
I will say.
Yes.
And that's it.
So telegram is connected to us.
So let me show you the telegram
here.
I am connected to the telegram web.
And you can see.
I have given the option to start
here.
It is still not responding to us.
Because we have not completed the
setup yet.
But let's go back here.
To the Hermes agent.
And here.
You don't need to worry about all of
these things.
Click on enter.
And the browser is asking.
What do you want.
And put the same thing.
Local browser.
And after that.
I don't want any additional user ID.
I don't want any of the
subscriptions.
Click on skip.
And Microsoft says free.
I will keep it as it is right now.
And I will also skip all of these
things.
I don't want any of these.
And it is asking again.
So let's do the same thing again.
And let's put the local browser.
And I don't need any subscription.
I don't need any image model.
Microsoft TTS.
And let me skip all of these things.
And I think that's it guys.
Once the setup is done.
Now the Hermes agent is currently live.
So if I just say.
Hello or hi.
It should respond back to us.
Okay.
There is an issue.
What does it say.
Error code 401.
There is an error.
But.
With our API key.
We got it right.
Why would we get an error.
I don't know why.
After a couple of minutes.
Of doing a debugging.
I got a solution.
That solution is.
Maybe it could be a bug.
You come here.
And you click on keys.
And after it comes down.
Click on anthropic.
And then.
Look here.
When we put the API key.
It is taking 200.
And it is taking extra information.
In our API key.
There is no such information.
That is why.
The API key is not working properly.
I will click on replace.
And I will paste my exact API key.
And I will click on save.
We saved the API key.
So what do we do.
Let me just restart the gateway.
So that.
The API key is getting a new load.
Okay.
Session restarted.
Guys.
Now let's see.
If we can talk to this agent.
Hello.
Look.
How can I help you today.
So I can ask a lot of questions.
Maybe.
Let's say.
Can you.
Look.
At the.
YouTube channel.
Named.
Balaji Chippada.
Can you summarize.
What.
He.
Does.
So let's see.
It should do an.
Google search.
But let's see.
And.
Now it got the information.
For the first time.
It did a lot of setup.
To write code.
To create an environment.
Every single thing it did.
Without any intervention.
Look.
And it gave me the on output.
Balaji Chippada.
YouTube channel summary.
24.5 subscribers.
Total 106 videos.
What do I do.
Content breakdown.
And what is the recent content.
Agentic road maps.
Every single thing it pulled out.
From the website.
And it got me the information.
In a single command.
I didn't do anything.
That is why.
This is so powerful.
But.
One of the issue is.
How can you come here.
And that is why.
It can support.
The telegram.
Multiple things.
So let's see.
Let's see.
Let's talk from here.
Let's say hello.
Let's see.
Let's see if it replies to this
agent.
Look.
Hi Balaji.
How can I help you today.
Actually we didn't say Balaji to it.
We didn't do anything.
But why did it say Balaji.
Do you know the answer.
Because.
It already pulled it from YouTube.
So it remembers or it knows that I
am Balaji.
And that is why it is saying.
Hi Balaji.
So it learns as you progress.
And as you use it actually.
That is why it is so powerful.
So from here.
Now you.
You can use the agent from the
telegram itself.
So let me zoom out a little bit.
But it's just like a chart.
So it can do a lot of things for us
using anthropic model.
But isn't it interesting if it can
pull the details from my calendar.
And that is what we are going to do
the next step.
Connecting our Google services
Google Gmail and calendar and
sheets to this agent.
So this agent can do tasks for us
autonomously.
Now if we want to connect our Google
services to Hermes agent.
You need permission from Google
right.
So how does that work.
By authentication.
So what you need to do for that is
you need to come to this website
console dot cloud
dot google dot com and say log in
with the account that you want to
connect to Hermes
agent.
After that you can search for
projects here.
And see there is a creative project
right.
Click on creative project.
And here I am going to give the name
of the project.
Hermes agent project one.
And click on create.
And here the project is created.
Then you can select this project.
We have come to the home page.
In the home page we are selecting
with Hermes agent project one.
Click on APIs and services.
And inside this you need to enable
the service.
Enable APIs.
And I want this agent to connect to
Gmail.
And Gmail API.
And click on this one.
And enable it.
And then same thing what you will
do.
You will also give permission to
calendar.
Google calendar API.
And then click on enable.
Next what we will do is we will also
enable drive.
So that we have some documents on
the drive.
And we will say drive API.
And click on this one.
And click on enable.
If you want this you can give
permission to it.
Google sheets.
Google forms.
People.
A lot of stuff.
But for now let us click on email.
And then calendar.
And then drive.
So that is the second step.
And after that you need to go to the
authentication overview.
Authentication consent screen is
there.
Click on this one.
And click on get started.
And here app name is there.
You can provide any kind of app
name.
Let us say external.
And here you provide your email that
you are using with.
And click on next.
And put external in audience.
And give the same email in contact
information.
I will provide my email.
And click on next.
And I will agree to this usage
details.
And click on continue.
And click on create.
And after that click on audience.
And here click on add users.
Here give your email.
Balaji Chippada dot 20 at the right
gmail dot com.
Click on save.
And yep.
We have added it to the test user.
Now we need to create the
authentication.
Click on overview.
And click on create authentication
client.
Click on this.
And let us say authentication type
web application.
And then we will create this one.
And here see our OAuth client is
created.
After creating you need to copy all
of these things.
If not you can download the json
directly.
And I will download my json.
And this is very important.
You need to save this very securely.
Now let us go back to telegram.
Here we will say.
I want to connect to my google
services.
Using the json provided here.
And I will provide the json file.
We have downloaded the json file.
And I will pass it to this Hermes
agent.
Now Hermes agent will set it up for
us.
We don't have to do anything.
Automatically it will do it for us.
Already it is in the skill.
Let me look at the file and check if
it is in the element skill or not.
And it is itself writing the code.
It is doing every single thing.
Now what does it say?
Not yet authenticated.
Before we proceed just two quick
questions.
What google services do you need?
Email, email plus calendar,
drive, everything, full workspace,
access, advanced production.
It is confidence web application.
For this to work desktop app.
It is not a web application but a
desktop app.
So what we will do.
We will go back to the
authentication client.
Click on ok.
Click on clients.
Let me delete the previous one.
We don't need it basically.
And click on create client.
And here we will say desktop app.
And click on create.
And click on download json.
Let us save this json.
So I got the new json.
So let me go back here and in
telegram let me put that.
And I will say here is the new
authentication json for the
workspace using desktop
app.
Desktop app.
I did this because if you do any
mistake this agent will teach you
what to do correctly.
And that is why you don't even need
to know coding.
This agent will do all of this for
us and it will guide us what to do
and what not
to do as well.
So client save is done.
Just let me know which services you
need and I will generate the
authorization url
for you to complete.
I want to connect to google drive
and calendar and email.
Let me generate the authorization
shell.
Let's see.
It will write the code.
It will execute everything inside
the terminal itself.
Need to install the dependencies.
Everything it will do it for us
guys.
And once we connect all of these
things and it will be very easy to
use.
This is all first hand setup.
Dependence is already installed.
Let me generate the authentication
url.
Look.
Now the url will come.
Click on this url and we have to
authenticate.
Very simple.
So here it says if you get an access
denied error go to all of these
things.
And now let's look at authorize
Hermes agent.
Click on open.
And I will provide this email and I
will click on continue.
And I will select all of the things
that I want to give access to and
click on continue.
And here we got an error.
This site cannot be reached.
What will I do now?
I will just copy this one and then I
will put it here.
Look.
Copy the entire url from the
browser's address bar.
It will look like HTTP localhost.
I know this will give an error.
But it is asking me to copy paste
the error.
And I will just put it here.
And that's exactly what I
expected.
Let me change the code for the token
now.
Look.
Let's see.
Let me verify.
Everything is working.
You are all set up.
Google workspace is now connected
with access to Gmail, Google
calendar, Google drive,
sheets, contacts, every single
thing.
Now the interesting thing.
What will I do now?
I will show you my calendar for
Sunday.
This is what my calendar would look
like.
6.30 to 8.30.
There are a lot of things that are
blocked for me to plan my day.
Now, I will give a command to the
Hermes agent.
I will say, can you look
at my calendar
for tomorrow and plan
my day accordingly?
So, I just didn't do anything.
I didn't give the date.
I didn't give anything.
So, the agent has to think about it.
It was date 20, today's date 20.
And it should pull the details from
the calendar.
And it should give me every single
thing.
And look quickly.
Here is your agent.
It's a packed content creation day.
6.30 to 8.30 chest day.
And then 8.30 to 10.
It's a free block.
10 to 12.30 I have to do my video.
12.30 to 13.30 is free again.
And 13.30 to 4.30 I need to do a
Sunday live.
And 14.30 to 6.30 it needs to do a
Agentic Roadmap video.
6.30 to 8.
There is a free block.
8 to 12.
I have to edit again.
Key tips for tomorrow.
It's a long day.
Stay hydrated and use the morning
free block.
And the back -to -back live.
If there is a command,
it can work for me.
And maybe let's say we will also
schedule this task.
So can you schedule this task
like checking my
email every day
in the morning.
And can you send me a summary
like this at 8 am
daily.
So let's say I need this summary
every day.
What should I do now?
It needs to schedule a cron job.
So by default it will do this.
I will set up two daily cron jobs.
Morning email summary.
Checks for your email and sends you
the digest.
And daily calendar plan.
Looks at today's events and plan
your day.
And this is like a proper AI
assistant that is working for me.
So it created two cron jobs and two
created automatically.
I don't need to do anything.
So every day at 8 am it will give me
the message on the telegram.
I don't need to open the laptop as
well.
That is the advantage of running an
agent inside a VPS.
And now let's do one more complex
task.
This is my drive.
In this drive there is this file
which is called masterclass21.
What should this agent do?
It needs to send an email attaching
that file.
Check the google drive folder named
SQL masterclass.
Inside that folder you will find a
name like this.
And send it via email to Gautham
SPH1234.
You don't even need to put all of
these things.
Let's remove it.
I will remove all of these things.
By default it should do all of that.
So let's see if it does this.
And let's click on enter.
Let me search for the folder and the
file on your drive.
Now the drive is connected
automatically.
Found the folder.
Let me search for the files.
And this file will find out
masterclass2 and how to machines
learn and make decisions.
And it will download and send it via
email itself directly.
I don't need to open the drive or
the mail.
I don't need to do anything.
So it is asking to send an
attachment.
This is the subject.
Shall I go ahead and tell it.
Maybe I want to give some context to
the body.
I will say.
I will talk to the agent right now.
Maybe can you add the body like
Hey Gautham this is the masterclass
session that I have planned for the
upcoming session.
Can you please review it and give me
the feedback.
And let's click on enter.
See.
Self -improvement review user
profile updated.
It is learning from the discussions
that we are doing on a day to day
tasks.
Maybe can you add the body like
Hey Gautham this is the masterclass
session that I have planned for the
upcoming sessions.
Can you please review it and give me
the feedback.
Let me check if it is the other way.
But let's see.
No attachment support is there.
It is called CLI.
Let me send it via quick python
script.
It took an issue and that issue will
also be solved automatically.
Email sent successfully.
Gautham and attachment.
Subjects are all fine.
So let's go into our email and check
if the email has been sent.
And click on refresh.
And see.
Gautham SBH 1234.
SQL masterclass how machines learn
and make decisions with this
subject.
And with the same PDF.
Now it has opened the drive.
Downloaded it.
Error came.
Debugged the error.
Again everything was sent by email.
Everything autonomously.
And this is the power of running an
agent 24/7 on a VPS.
And that is what I wanted to teach
you.
In this video.
I know this video is a very lengthy
video.
But these steps are very mandatory.
I hope you enjoyed this video.
And if you have enjoyed please let
me know.
If you have any queries please let
me know in the comment section
below.
And that's all for this one.